[Shaiapouf imitating Komugi] Hello?
Sir Pitou?
This is Komugi.
I'm fine, so please don't worry about me.
I'll be all right.
[laughs]
[Shaiapouf] And now Pitou
is also under my spell.
My lie is like a magic trick
that will release him
from the curse of that girl.
[Neferpitou] Gon…
you respected my wishes
and waited for me…
already dead.
[Gon gasps]
[wind blowing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Gon] Wait.
Why are you healing your own arm?
Please, you can do that
after you finish healing Kite.
Please just do it, okay?
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
ANGER X AND X LIGHT
[wings fluttering]
[Shaiapouf] The tables have been turned.
[Palm and Killua gasp]
Gon is almost certainly going
to be killed before too long.
I'll be glad to stop Pitou for you.
[electricity crackling]
[gasps]
[Killua] You'd better start running,
you son of a bitch.
You can leave her to my care.
I swear upon these eyes that
I will never let them have her.
Gon, just hang on until I get there.
[Gon crying]
[exoskeleton crackling]
[Neferpitou] Gon…
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid…
I have to kill you now…
[Gon] You have to kill me?
So you're not gonna heal him?
You aren't gonna heal Kite?
[wind blowing]
[chorus continues]
[Neferpitou] What…
[Gon] Enough.
I don't care what happens to me now.
[intense music playing]
I need…
all the power I'll ever have.
[Neferpitou] I knew it.
I was right about him.
As I feared,
his fangs might even sink into the King.
[Gon] I'm gonna kill you.
Pitou!
[intense music playing]
Dance beyond my limit!
I have to stop him here and now.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[Neferpitou] I don't know how he did it,
but he's forced his body to mature
to an age where he can defeat me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[groans]
[Neferpitou groaning]
[Gon] Jan… ken.
Rock.
[Neferpitou gasps]
[narrator] At the edge
of fading consciousness,
Pitou was relieved.
[Neferpitou] Thank goodness.
There's only one way he could
have achieved this power,
by compressing his own life.
He was prepared
to burn himself out completely
and never be able to use Nen again.
-That was the resolve required to do this.
-[explosion]
[birds squawking]
[Neferpitou] This boy was born
with an incredible gift,
[footsteps pounding]
[chorus vocalizing]
[Neferpitou] Thank goodness
I was the one to die.
[rustling]
to race to Gon's location,
Killua arrived just in time to hear…
-[whoosh]
-[Killua gasps]
[boom]
[whoosh]
[narrator] …an unfamiliar silhouette,
one he had seen never before,
and a fist stained with blood
from countless blows.
That fist smashed Pitou's head
to a pulp,
though Pitou lay limp as a rag.
Jan… ken.
So…
[narrator] Having seen
Gon's appearance,
Killua immediately thought of Biscuit.
However, he realized
the difference in an instant.
But Gon's done the complete opposite.
[dramatic music playing]
How many years?
More than ten? Decades?
This is what he would look like
after years and years of training.
[imperceptible]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[slice]
[narrator] Pitou's Terpsichora,
with aura amplified by death,
It doesn't hurt. I'm not bluffing.
I'm actually kind of happy.
Finally…
I can be just like Kite was in the end.
[Killua] Gon.
[Gon] I feel…
a little better now.
Show me Rock.
[gasps] Gon, no!
[Killua] Gon, stop it, please.
Don't use any more power.
How much will you have to pay?
It's too much.
Jan…
ken.
[closing theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Flash and Start."
[singer singing in Japanese]